As times change, difficult cases increase in number!
تتضاعف القضايا المعقّدة مع مضيّ خط الوقت
Today's stage is a coffee shop!
مسرح اليوم هو مقهى
Is a customer to blame?!
هل زبون مجهول هو الفاعل؟
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله لبالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
Where are you going, Ran-neechan?
أين تذهبين يا ران-نيتشان؟
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
Are you going to the movies? I wanna come too!
!ستذهبين للسينما؟ أريد الذهاب معك
No! I have a date!
!صه! كلا، لديّ موعد
A date?
موعد؟
With Shinichi!
مع شينتشي
Oh, with Shinichi?
هكذا إذاً، مع شينتشي-نيتشان؟
Dad would get mad if he found out,
سيغضب أبي إن عرف بالأمر لذا اكتم الأمر عنه، اتّفقنا؟
Sure! Have fun!
!أجل، مع السلامة
Ran sure is dressed up...
تكلّفت ران في اللبس هكذا
Is she really that happy to go on a date with me?
أهي سعيدة لهذا الحدّ للخروج في موعد معي؟
She can't do that!
!لا يمكنها ذلك
I'm Kudo Shinichi!
!فأنا كودو شينتشي
Then who is she going out with?!
من الذي ستقابله في موعدٍ إذاً؟
Why would she lie like that?!
اختلقت كذبةً لذلك حتّى
I sound stupid.
حماقة
Ran can go out with whoever she wants...
يمكن لران الخروج مع من تشاء
Didn't I tell you I was going on a date today?
ألم أخبرك أنّي سأذهب لموعد اليوم؟
Why did you follow me?
لمَ تبعتني؟
I wanted to see Shinichi too!
!لأنّي أريد رؤية شينتشي-نيتشان أيضاً
But he sure is late...
...لكنّه تأخّر
The truth is, the person coming isn't actually Shinichi--
...في الحقيقة يا كونان-كن، من سأقابله اليوم ليس شينتشي
Eh? Then who are you really meeting?
ماذا؟ من إذاً الذي كذبتِ بشأن لقائه؟
Well?
من؟
Somebody really dear to me, I guess you can say!
شخصٌ عزيز عليّ... كثيراً
Even more so than Shinichi?
أكثر من شينتشي-نيتشان حتّى؟
Don't be silly! I can't compare the two!
أحمق! لا يمكنني مقارنتهما
Say, can't you go home now?
ما رأيك بأن ترجع للبيت الآن؟
I suddenly don't feel like going home...
لم أعد أشعر برغبة في العودة لسببٍ ما
I know! You like cake, don't you?
وجدتُها، ألستَ تحب الكعك؟
I'll go buy you some now,
سأشتري لك واحدة لذا كُن مطيعاً وخذها وارجع
Sorry, I'll be right back!
آسفة، سأعود فوراً
Sure!
حسناً
It's pointless, Ran.
لا جدوى يا ران
With my powers of perception and deduction,
بقدراتي في الملاحظة والاستنتاج
I'll figure out exactly who it is you're meeting and get a good look at 'em!
سأكتشف من ستلتقينه وأمعن النظر في وجهه
'Cuz there's always only one truth!
لأنّ الحقيقة واحدة دوماً
Welcome!
!مرحباً
Oh, it's just a woman.
إنّها امرأة
Are you by yourself? If so, then please sit--
...أأنتِ بمفردك؟ يمكنك الجلوس عند المنضدة
Miss!
!آنستي
Coffee.
قهوة
Haven't you ever heard of coffee?! Go get me some!
!القهوة تعني القهوة! هاتي كأساً بسرعة
Talk about a bad attitude!
!يا لسلوك تلك المرأة
Oh? She's fixated on her watch.
ماذا؟ تشغلها ساعتها أيمكن أنّها هي؟
Yeah, right. After all...
...مستحيل، فهو
It's somebody really dear to me!
شخصٌ عزيز عليّ
...so I doubt it.
...لذا أشكّ
Welcome! Are you by yourself?
مرحباً، أأنت بمفردك؟ ...في تلك الحالة
I, uh, have a paper I have to write...
المعذرة، لديّ بحثٌ عليّ إنهاؤه
I'd like a quiet seat, if possible...
لذا أفضّل مقعداً هادئاً
A college student...
طالب جامعيّ
I don't think it's him, either...
لا يبدو أنّه هو أيضاً
Cafe au lait, please...
قهوة بالحليب من فضلك
Nobody would write a paper
فلا أحد سيكتب بحثاً أمام شخص سيلتقيه
A lady this time...
امرأة هذه المرّة
Welcome!
مرحباً
I'm meeting someone, but they don't seem to be here yet...
اتّفقت مع أحدهم على اللقاء هنا، لكن لا يبدو أنّه وصل بعد
May I get you something?
أيمكنني أخذ طلبك؟
Kisaki Eri (37)
(37) كيساكي إيري
I guess I'll have some coffee.
سأختار قهوة
Man, she's pretty!
!يا لجمالها
A law office? Is she an attorney?
مكتب محاماة؟ أهي محامية؟
Ran wouldn't be meeting with a lawyer.
يستحيل أن تلتقي ران بمحامية
Yikes! I got her mad!
!تبّاً! ستوبّخني
Eh? Mad?
ماذا؟ توبّخني؟
All I did was look at her...
...كلّ ما فعلته هو النظر لها، فلمَ
Hey there!
!مرحباً أيّها الساقي
Oh, Tonoyama-san!
تونوياما-سان، ما حلّ بإصبعك؟
Sprained it during rugby practice.
(تونوياما جوزو (38
Can't fit my wedding ring on it now!
لا أستطيع إدخال خاتم زواجي الآن
No! It's not him!
كلا، ليس هو
It's unlikely that someone who's going to meet someone else
فمن المستبعد أن يتجه شخص سيلتقي أحدهم لطاولة الشراب مباشرةً دون النظر في المكان
Oh? Did you cut your hair?
ماذا؟ هل قصصت شعرك؟
Yeah, I was gettin' kinda shaggy...
أجل، فكان قد بدأ يزعجني
Hey, where's the bathroom?
أين دورة المياه؟
Right back there.
من هناك
I see.
هكذا إذاً
But it's unisex here.
لكنّها دورة مياه مشتركة
I know.
أعرف
I guess it doesn't matter...
ربما لا يهمّ
Back to Ran's meeting!
أعود لموعد ران
The fact they haven't shown up yet must mean they're already here...
عدم ظهور الطرف الثاني بعد يعني أنّه موجود بالفعل
Welcome!
!مرحباً
Are you by yourself?
أأنت بمفردك؟
I'm meeting a girl here,
اتّفقت مع فتاة على اللقاء هنا لكن يبدو أنّها لم تأت بعد
Then please take that seat!
اجلس هنا إذاً من فضلك
Yeah.
حسناً
Some coffee for now.
قهوة ساخنة للآن
Don't tell me it's this loser!
...أيمكن، أيمكن أنّه
Wakaoji here! Oh, hey, Yoshio...
!مرحباً، معك واكاوجي
It's that cute chick who toured the TV station the other day.
إنّها الفتاة الظريفة التي أتت لمحطّة التلفاز في جولة ذاك اليوم
TV station?!
محطّة التلفاز؟
The one where that producer was killed?!
التي قُتل فيها المُنتج؟
She's strangely innocent for girls these days!
إنّها بريئة لحدٍّ نادر بالنسبة لفتيات هذه الأيام
What do you mean, watch myself?
مثلها يكنّ منيعات؟
Just treat girls like objects and they'll be all yours!
!عامل الفتيات سأغراض... وسيصبحن لك
Bastard!
!الوغد
Yeah, I'll make sure none of my other girls find out.
أجل، سأحرص على ألّا تكتشف بقية الفتيات
See ya.
إلى اللقاء
Alright, watch this!
سأريك
I'll use these Power Kick Shoes to bust that pretty face of yours!
سأستعمل حذاء مضاعفة قوّة الركل هذا !لسحق وجهك الأهبل
Edogawa-sama!
!إيدوغاوا-ساما
Is there an Edogawa-sama here?
أيوجد إيدوغاوا-ساما بين الزبائن؟
That's me...
إنّه أنا
You have a call, little boy!
اتّصال لك يا فتى
Thanks.
شكراً
Hello?
مرحباً؟
Conan-kun?
كونان-كن؟
Ran-neechan!
!ران-نيتشان
I'm sorry! I won't be back right away!
آسفة، لا يمكنني الرجوع بعد
The cash register broke, so I can't get my change!
آلة حساب المتجر لا تعمل ولا أستطيع أخذ فكّتي
Say, has anybody come looking for me?
أخبرني، هل أتى أحد يبحث عنّي؟
I saw 'em. They had long hair.
رأيت الشخص، طويل الشعر
Yeah, that's them!
!أجل، صحيح! ذاك هو
But that's strange-- their hair is usually tied...
...لكن غريب، لطالما كان الشعر مربوطاً
Yeah they just tied it up.
أجل، ربطه للتو
Forget about meeting them, Ran-neechan.
...انسي أمره يا ران-نيتشان، لا تلتقي بشاكلته
Wait!
!ا-انتظري
Darn it! When that long-haired jerk leaves the bathroom--
...تبّاً! لحظة مغادرة الوغد طويل الشعر ذاك للحمّام
What is it?!
!ماذا هناك؟
Blood?!
!دم؟
Wait, kid!
!انتظر يا فتى
Huh? Something's blocking it!
!ماذا؟ يسدّه أحدهم
What the--?!
!ماذا؟
I'm late! I bet they're mad!
!تبّاً! تأخّرت! لا بدّ أنّ ذاك الشخص غاضبٌ الآن
Huh? What's this?
ماذا؟ ماذا هناك؟
Did something happen here?
أحصل شيءٌ هنا؟
There was a murder!
جريمة قتل
A murder?!
!جريمة قتل؟
Don't tell me that person was involved?!
أيمكن أنّه علق فيها؟
Just as this photo shows, the victim fell to the floor
كما تظهر هذه الصورة، كانت الضحيّة على الأرض بجسدها يسدّ الباب
Is that right, Conan-kun?
أليس كذلك يا كونان-كن؟
Yeah. The door was unlocked but it wouldn't open
أجل، كان القفل مفتوحاً لكن الباب لا يُفتح فنظرت من الأعلى
The victim was Himeno Yayoi, 24 years old.
الضحيّة هي هيمينو يايوي، 24 عاماً. عاطلة
A single stab to the heart...
طعنة واحدة في القلب
Inspector.
حضرة المفتّش
There's a thin mark on her throat, as if she had been choked!
توجد علامات خنق رفيعة على عنقها
Judging from the blood splatter,
،بناءً على بقع الدماء
the killer probably strangled her unconscious, stabbed her,
فقد خنقها القاتل حتّى فقدت وعيها ثمّ طعنها
She had probably seen the killer's face...
رأت وجهه فشعر بالهلع بالتأكيد
This was the work of a mugger...
كانت فعلة لصّ غالباً
The open window and stall door...
...النافذة المفتوحة وباب الحجرة
The back alley just outside...
الرواق الخلفي الفارغ
The empty wallet next to the murder weapon...
المحفظة الفارغة بجوار سلاح الجريمة وأغراض الضحيّة
And then the victim's body, which blocked the stall door...
كما جثّة الضحية التي سدّت باب الحجرة
In other words, the killer entered through the window,
،مما يعني أنّ القاتل دخل من النافذة ،وانتظر قدوم أحدهم
killed Himeno-san, who just happened to come in,
،وقتل هيمينو-سان الذي صادف أنّها دخلت
stole her money, and quickly escaped out the window.
وسرق مالها ثمّ لاذ بالفرار سريعاً من النافذة
Alright! This was an outside job!
!حسنٌ، كانت جريمة خارجية
Investigate the surrounding area!
!فتّشوا المنطقة المجاورة
Hold on a second, Inspector!
!انتظر سيّدي المفتّش
Look at that window! Doesn't it seem too clean?
انظر لتلك النافذة! ألا تبدو نظيفةً لحدٍّ مُريب؟
What's wrong with a clean bathroom?
أين المشكلة في حمّام نظيف؟
That's not what I mean!
!لم أقصد ذلك
He's right, Assistant Inspector Megure.
الولد محقّ أيّها المفتّش المساعد ميغوري
Oh, is it just "Inspector" now?
أم أنّك أصبحت مفتّشاً الآن؟
Oh, you're Ms. Kisaki!
!أنتِ المحامية كيساكي
What are you doing here?
ماذا تفعلين هنا؟
I just happened to be in the coffee shop.
صادف أن كنتُ في هذا المقهى
Do you know her, Inspector?
أتعرفها حضرة المفتّش؟
Yes, she's--
...أجل، فهي
At any rate, judging from the amount of blood loss,
،بأيّ حال، بناءً على كميّة الدماء المفقودة من الضحيّة
the killer should have been sprayed with blood.
يُفترض أن توجد بقع دماء على القاتل
Yet there are no traces of blood on the window used to escape.
مع ذلك لا آثار للدماء على النافذة التي هرب منها
This is unnatural!
هذا غير طبيعيّ
But the killer could've wiped it off!
لكن يمكن أنّ القاتل مسحها
Would a killer who hastily escaped without the murder weapon
هل سيفعل قاتل رمى سلاح الجريمة وهرب هلعاً
do something like that?
شيئاً كذلك؟
They left it there because they couldn't take it with them!
ترك سلاح الجريمة لأنّه لا يستطيع أخذه
Yes. This was an inside job!
أجل، كانت جريمة داخلية
It was someone in this restaurant!
كان أحداً من الموجودين في المقهى
That's what you want to say, right, little boy?
أليس ذلك ما أردت قوله يا ولد؟
But Kisaki-san!
لكن يا كيساكي-سان
The body was blocking the stall door!
كانت الجثّة تسدّ باب الحجرة
There are no signs of the body being moved,
لا علامات على نقل الجثة ولا نافذة في الحجرة المجاورة
How did the killer leave the stall?!
كيف غادر القاتل الحجرة؟
There is only one way. From above.
توجد طريقة واحدة، من الأعلى
Above? You mean that gap?!
من الأعلى؟ قصدك تلك الفجوة؟
No adult could fit through that--
لا يمكن لبالغ المرور منها
You. Could you try climbing it?
أيمكنك محاولة صعودها؟
In the next stall, so as not to disturb the evidence.
الحجرة المجاورة كيلا نعبث بمسرح الجريمة
I can just manage to fit...
مررت بطريقةٍ ما
See?
رأيت؟
But if the killer was covered in blood,
،لكن إن كان القاتل مُغطى بالدماء
there should be blood on the wall too!
يُفترض أن تكون هناك آثار على الحائط عندما صعد
Luckily, there's water and paper in here to wipe it off.
لحسن الحظّ يوجد ماء لغسل الدمّ وورق للمسح
They could've had it planned out to not leave any traces!
فبإمكانه صعود الحائط دون ترك آثار
But what if someone accidentally walked in and saw them?!
لكن ماذا لو دخل أحدٌ صدفة ورآه؟
Oh, you didn't notice?
لم تلحظ؟
The restroom door has a lock.
لباب مدخل دورة المياه قفل
Locking it would make this room impenetrable.
إقفاله يعني أنّ الغرفة ستكون عديمة المداخل
Alright! Find everyone who came in here around the time the victim did!
حـ-حسنٌ! جِدوا جميع من دخلوا دورة المياه !وقت دخول الضحيّة
I know who did!
!أنا أعرفهم
I just happened to see!
فقد رأيتهم صدفةً
Really?
حقاً؟
There was that big guy over there,
كان أحدهم ذاك الشخص ضخم البنية
that guy who didn't shave,
والشخص بشعر الوجه الخفيف
and that snobby ponytail guy!
والشاب المختال بالشعر المربوط
And this lady too!
كـ-كما... هذه العمّة
You used the restroom too?!
ذهبتِ لدورة المياه أيضاً؟
I did, now that you mention it.
أجل، بذكرك ذلك
You have a good memory, little boy...
لديك ذاكرة جيّدة يا ولد، أحسنت
Now then, can you tell us why you came here today,
حسناً يا سادة، هلّا أخبرتمونا لمَ أتيتم اليوم
in order of who used the restroom?
بترتيب دخولكم لدورة المياه؟
Yes, I came here today to write my paper...
حسناً، أتيتُ هنا لكتابة بحث اليوم
I went in next, while the victim was still inside.
دخلتُ بعده بينما لا زالت الضحية في الداخل
I came here to meet someone.
أتيتُ للمقهى للقاء أحدهم
I went in next.
دخلت بعدها
I come here almost everyday to chat with the bartender.
آتي يومياً للكلام مع الساقي
I was the last one to go in.
أنا آخر من دخل
I was waiting for a girl.
كنتُ أنتظر فتاة
Is that the order they went in, Conan-kun?
أكان هذا الترتيب السليم يا كونان-كن؟
Yes...
...أ-أجل
What could it be?
ما هناك؟
Something seems different from before...
أشعر باختلاف شيءٍ عن قبل
That was an easy fit.
كان ذلك مروراً يسيراً
You're next, Wakaoji-san.
أنتَ التالي يا واكاوجي-سان
Yeah.
حـ-حسناً
Doesn't look like I can fit!
لا-لا يمكنني المرور وفقما يبدو
Hey, now!
مهلك
I guess you really couldn't, huh?
ربما لا يمكنك حقاً يا أخّ
Do I have to do it too?
هل عليّ فعل ذلك أيضاً؟
No. You'd never fit.
كلا، يستحيل ذلك
Kisaki-san, I take it you don't need to?
أفترض أنّ لا حاجة لتجربي يا كيساكي-سان
Yes, I'm sure I could easily fit.
كلا، فيمكنني المرور بلا مشكلة
It would seem this narrows the suspects down to Sumeragi-san and myself.
هذا يقلّص قائمة المشتبه بهم لي وسوميراغي-سان
No, of course I don't suspect you!
!كلا، لا أشتبه بك أبداً
Inspector!
حضرة المفتش! وجدنا هذا الحبل !على طاولة سوميراغي-سان
What?!
ماذا؟
Sumeragi-san! Is this yours?!
سوميراغي-سان، أيخصّك هذا؟
That's just some string I use to tie my books together!
!إنّه مجرد شريط أستعمله لربط كتبي ودفتر ملاحظاتي
I'm not the killer! Honest!
!لستُ القاتل! إنها الحقيقة
He entered the restroom before the victim;
دخل دورة المياه قبل الضحيّة
he didn't do it.
إنه ليس القاتل
She asked the bartender where the restroom was.
سألت الضحيّة الساقي عن مكان دورة المياه
This was probably a sign to let the killer know
كانت إشارةً للقاتل على أنّها ستذهب لدورة المياه غالباً
Which means the only person in the coffee shop then
ما يعني أنّ الشخص الوحيد الذي كان موجوداً ...في المقهى وقتها وبإمكانه ارتكاب الجريمة
...was Ms. Kisaki!
!هو المحامية كيساكي فحسب
Inspector.
حضرة المفتّش، أيمكننا أخذ السكّين للمركز؟
Yes, that's fine.
أجل، لا مشكلة
Understood.
حسناً
Let me see that!
!دعني أرى
Hey, kid!
!أنت، يا فتى
This knife is odd!
هذه السكّين غريبة
Why is there blood on the handle?!
لمَ يوجد دم على الممسك؟
And why is there no blood on this narrow part?!
كما لمَ لا توجد دماء على هذا الجزء الضيّق؟
There's blood on my palm!
يوجد دم على راحة يدي ...مع أنّي لم ألمس الجثّة
I must've gotten it when I looked over the stall!
ربما انتقل عندما نظرتُ فوق الباب
What was blood doing up there?
لمَ كان هناك دم في الأعلى؟
I seriously doubt the body put it there!
..أشكّ أن الجثة نقلته هناك
Now I understand the killer's real trick!
!فهمت الآن الحيلة الحقيقية التي استعملها القاتل
No doubt about it!
،لا شكّ في الأمر
Only that person could've done this!
!إنّه الوحيد القادر على فعل هذا
But I have no proof!
...لكن لا دليل لديّ
That's enough of your detective game, little boy!
!يكفي من لعبة التحرّي يا ولد
This is grownup work!
هذا عمل بالغين
Learn your place as a child!
على الأطفال معرفة حدودهم
But, uh--
...لكن، أنا
A wedding ring!
خاتم زواج
This is it! If my logic is correct,
،ها هو! إن أصاب استنتاجي !سيكون دليلاً قاطعاً
Alright, Sumeragi-san.
،إذاً يا سوميراغي-سان
I have to ask you to come to the station.
هلّا رافقتنا للمركز؟
Eh?! I didn't kill anyone!
!لم أقتل أحداً
Oh! There's blood up here!
!ماذا؟ يوجد دم هنا
Oh, I found that too when I was taking photos of the scene.
وجدتُه أيضاً عندما كنت ألتقط صوراً لمسرح الجريمة
Why didn't you say so sooner?!
لمَ لم تخبرني قبلاً؟
Anyway, Sumeragi-san.
،بأيّ حال يا سوميراغي-سان
You're starting to look more and more suspicious...
الشبهة حولك تزداد أكثر فأكثر
You can't be serious...
...لا-لا يمكن
But isn't it strange?
لكن أليس الأمر غريباً؟
The blood was on the top of the door that the body was blocking.
كان الدم فوق الباب الذي تسدّه الجثة
If it were me, I would use the toilet
لو كنت مكانه، لاستعملت المرحاض لأتسلّق للحجرة المجاورة
You do have a point...
...معك حق
And I wonder if the killer really was sprayed with blood...
وأتساءل إن كان القاتل مغطى بالدماء حقاً؟
Just take a look at that bag!
انظر للكيس الذي يحمله الشرطيّ
Even the handle is covered in blood!
السكّين مليئة ببقع الدمّ حتّى الممسك
Yes, that is strange.
هذا غريب بالفعل
But what's this part that has no blood on it?
وما هذا الجزء الخالي من الدم؟
Something might've been tied there.
ربما كان هناك شيء مربوط حوله
Aha! The killer tied a string to it, stabbed her,
،فهمت! ربط القاتل خيطاً بالسكّين وطعنها
and then pulled it out after leaving the stall!
!ثم سحبّها بعد مغادرة الحجرة
The blood sprayed out when the knife was removed!
!تطاير الدم عندما سُحبت السكين
But then why is there blood up there if the killer wasn't sprayed with any?
لكن لمَ يوجد دم في الأعلى إذا لم يصب القاتل شيئاً منه؟
Because it wasn't the killer who went over the stall,
لأنّ القاتل ليس من صعد الحجرة
it was the body that did.
بل الجثّة
The body went over it?!
الجثّة؟
The blood above the door got there
وصل الدم فوق الباب
when the victim was being dumped into the stall.
عندما رُميت الضحيّة للحجرة
The killer stabbed her outside the stall,
طعنها القاتل خارج الحجرة
threw the body into it, and blocked the door.
ثمّ رمى جثتها داخلها وسدّ الباب
The knife was then pulled out with a tug on the string.
وسحب السكّين بجرّه للخيط
This way, if it were discovered to be an inside job,
،هكذا حتى لو اُكتشف أنّها جريمة داخلية
the killer could avoid suspicion
يمكن للقاتل تفادي الشُبهات
due to being unable to fit over the stall door.
بما أنّ ليس بإمكانه المرور فوق باب الحجرة
Are you saying the killer was--
...أتقصدين أنّ القاتل
You, Tonoyama-san!
!لا يمكن أن يكون سواك يا تونوياما-سان
Alright! Take this man into custody!
!حسنٌ، اعتقلوا هذا الرجل
Can you really arrest me without proof?
أيمكنكم اعتقالي حقاً دون دليل؟
Of course we have proof!
لدينا دليل بالطبع
Right, Kisaki-san?
صحيح يا كيساكي-سان؟
No.
كلا
Even if you did arrest him,
،حتّى لو اعتقلتموه
it would only take me a few hours to prove his innocence.
لن تستغرقني أكثر من بضع ساعات لإبرائه لو كنتُ محاميته
Naturally!
بالطبع
I only came here today to chat with the bartender!
فقد أتيتُ اليوم للحديث مع الساقي فحسب
Yeah, I heard you!
أجل، سمعتك
You sprained your finger playing rugby!
لويت إصبعك أثناء لعب الرغبي
Oh? Don't people wear wedding rings on their left ring finger?
ماذا؟ ألا يضع الناس خاتم الزواج على بنصرهم الأيسر غالباً؟
Your bandage was on your ring finger when you entered the coffee shop.
كانت ضمادتك على بنصرك عندما دخلت المقهى، أليس كذلك؟
Maybe you refastened it in the bathroom?
ربما... أعدت ربطها في دورة المياه؟
That's it! That bandage was the string used
هكذا إذاً! الضمادة كانت الخيط الذي !استعمله لخنق الضحيّة كما ما رُبط بالسكّين
Which means the victim's blood should be on it!
!ما يعني أنّ دم الضحية عليها بالتأكيد
My, my. What a foolish criminal you are
عجباً، يا للمجرم الساذج
to keep this kind of evidence on you.
احتفظتَ بدليل كهذا عليك
Not even I could defend you in court!
حتّى أنا لا يمكنني الدفاع عنك في المحكمة
Move, woman!
!ابتعدي يا امرأة
Whoa! A one-armed shoulder throw!
!مُذهل! رمية كتف بيد واحدة
Let go, damn you!
!دعوني! تبّاً
Huh? I've seen that shoulder throw somewhere before...
لحظة، رأيتُ رمية كتف اليد الواحدة هذه ...قبلاً في مكانٍ ما
Thanks to the female attorney, the killer was arrested without incident.
اُعتقل القاتل بلا حوادث بفضل المُحامية
Apparently, he did it because he was having an affair with the victim,
يبدو أنّ سبب الجريمة كان علاقته غير الشرعية مع الضحيّة
and she threatened to tell his wife if he didn't marry her.
وتهديدها له بإخبار زوجته إذا لم يتزوّجها
Now to do something about this snob who's meeting Ran.
حسناً، عليّ فعل شيء حيال هذا !المختال الذي سيلتقي ران
Ran!
!ران
Sorry I'm so late! I didn't mean to!
!آسفة على التأخير! عانيت بالتأكيد
Jerk!
!الوغد
Hey, what did you mean by,
أخبرني، ما كان قصدك عندما قلت عامل الفتيات كأغراض وسيصبحن لك"؟"
Earlier, he said--
...قال ذلك قبلاً
Wait! Kid!
!انتظر! يا فتى
Nice to meet you!
!مرحباً
Who is this guy?
من هذا الشخص؟
Did he really say that, Conan-kun?!
أقال ذلك حقاً يا كونان-كن؟
Ah, Sonoko-chan!
!سونوكو-تشان
You did, didn't you?!
!أقلتها حقاً؟
There must be some mistake--
...لا بدّ أنّه خطأ ما
Wait, Sonoko-chan!
!انتظري يا سونوكو-تشان
Oh, he was waiting for Sonoko?
كان ينتظر سونوكو؟
Then who was Ran waiting for?!
من الذي كانت تنتظره ران إذاً؟
Oh, are you dressed like that again?
ترتدين ثياب كهذه مُجدداً؟
Didn't I tell you it's not good to wear short skirts?
ألم أخبرك أنّ ارتداء التنورات القصيرة سيصيب معدتك بالبرد؟
You don't need to keep treating me like a kid, Mom!
لا داعي لتعامليني كطفلة دوماً يا أمّي
M-Mo-- Eh?!
!أ-أ-أمّ... ماذا؟
What are you slinking behind me for?
لمَ تتخفّى ورائي هكذا؟
He was very remarkable earlier!
كان مفعماً بالقوّة حتّى قبل قليل
The case was solved thanks to him!
حُلّت القضيّة بفضله
Isn't that right, Conan-kun?
أليس كذلك يا كونان-كن؟
Oh, I don't think he likes me...
ماذا؟ يبدو أنّه لا يحبّني
Of course I don't!
بالطبع لا
You yelled at me and Ran all the time when we were kids!
فقد وبّختني على الدوام مع ران في صغرنا
I practically became allergic to you!
!أصبح جسدي يتفاعل لا إرادياً حولك
It's already been ten years since you left...
...بالمناسبة، مضت 10 أعوام مذ تركتِ البيت
What brought that up?
لمَ تذكرين هذا فجأةً؟
And in ten years, you've forgotten my face...
وتنسى وجه أحدهم بسهولة بعد 10 أعوام
I was just thinking you should come back to Dad soon...
كنتُ أفكر أنّ الوقت ملائم الآن لترجعي لأبي
Forget that! I despise that lazy, filthy, womanizing drunk!
!مستحيل، أُبغض ذاك المُغازل القذر الكسول الثمل
The only things I've gained from him
...كلّ ما استفدته منه
are you and that shoulder throw...
...هو أنت ورمية الكتف تلك
Then why did you marry him?
لمَ تزوّجته إذاً؟
We grew up together.
كبرنا معاً
Then what's with the wedding ring?
وما سبب ارتدائك لخاتم زواجك؟
A bug repellant to keep annoying men away.
طارد حشرات لإبعاد الرجال المزعجين
You're so stubborn!
!يا لعنادك
Not so fast, Matsuo-san! I must ask you to--
...انتظر يا ماتسو-سان
This is a clip of when Dad solved that case at the TV station!
هذا مقطع للقضيّة التي حلّها أبي على التلفاز مؤخراً
Didn't you say you wanted to see it?
ألم تقولي أنّك أردتِ رؤيته؟
Here is the phone call that was the key to solving the case.
ها هو الاتّصال الذي كان مفتاح حلّ القضيّة
My wife?
زوجتي؟
It's alright! We don't live together!
!لا تقلقي! فنحن لم نعد معاً
Let's have a passionate night tonight!
!لنقض ليلةً ساخنة اليوم
It's not what you think! He was--
...ليس كما تظنّين! كان
It seems I can't go back just yet.
يبدو ليس بإمكاني العودة بعد
Ran. You be careful of that detective you grew up with, too!
ران، احذري من المتحرّي صديق طفولتك أيضاً
He'll only get you into trouble!
تجنّبي التعاسة
Wait, Mom!
!انتظري يا أمّي
Why, you!
...يا وغد
Those guys don't seem like hikers!
لا يبدو أنّهما مُتنزهان
They have a shovel, but they're wearing suits!
لديهما مجرف كما يرتديان بذلاً
And what exactly is that map?!
وما كانت تلك الخريطة؟
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
"The Detective League Survival Case."
قضيّة نجاة فرقة فتيان التحرّي
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Homemade map.
خريطة كنز